<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chien Wei&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chien Wei&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 22:30:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://chienwei0319.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Inpress</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/inpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/inpress/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a phone holder could set your hands free with a gimmick on it and what&amp;rsquo;s more is it perfectly fit various sizes of mobiles. The product is called &amp;ldquo;Inpress&amp;rdquo;; you will be impress by a simply press. It&amp;rsquo;s featured by its washable silicon sticker attached under the base, it can offer a steady mobile ride while you&amp;rsquo;re driving; there is no more messy annoying situation and inconvenience for you to find a right position to drive and using navigation service at the same moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lollipop</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/lollipop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/lollipop/</guid>
      <description>D&amp;amp;D teamed up with AGIO to create Lollipop, one of the first products under the new AGIO+ brand. In a crowed market of overly &amp;ldquo;techy&amp;rdquo; action cameras, Lollipop takes a fresh approach to capturing the wonderful life&amp;rsquo;s moments whenever wherever you are. An affordable, high-quality, waterproof camera with a user-friendly design, Lollipop is about creating a new standard of enjoying and sharing your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BooGie</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/boogie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/boogie/</guid>
      <description>BooGie is designed to be a fun tech gadget by employing microphone and speaker function. With the bluetooth connection with smart phone, people can hold it and enjoy singing Karaoke songs streaming online. The upright body and off-ground speaker mechanical design make BooGie also a great speaker which can play music harmoniousely and broadly. It&amp;rsquo;s an entertainment product designed for parties, friends/family/colleagues/whatever reunions, road trip and camping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X7</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/x7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/x7/</guid>
      <description>X7 is YUMA&amp;rsquo;s first home appliances product. The transparent part not only display the stage of mood but light up and show off the atomization process, giving user a special pleasant experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pinbulb</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/pinbulb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/pinbulb/</guid>
      <description>Pinbulb, an innovation re-design of light bulb, is a solar lighting gear designed for people who want to settle outdoor luminous effortlessly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foldable Bike Trailer</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/foldable-bike-trailer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/foldable-bike-trailer/</guid>
      <description>Exspider Foldable Bike Trailer integrates carrying and style. This luggage system can tackle all situations, transforming between bicycle trailer, wheeled suitcase or luggage bag, even folding compact quickly for storage or travel. Uniquely and significantly the Foldable Bike Trailer is useful on all modes of transportation, helping you join up your bike journey.
Furthermore, it&amp;rsquo;s equipped with coated waterproof fabric and zipper, 8 inches inflatable tires, aluminum alloy and extra protection pad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitty</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/kitty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/kitty/</guid>
      <description>Kitty, the cation disinfection liquid atomizer, is aimed to clean up the in-door air rapidly within a simple touch. The minimalist kitty contour design gives the product a more fascinating feature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mosasaurus</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/mosasaurus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/mosasaurus/</guid>
      <description>Took inspiration for the yacht design from the ancient king of dinosaur- Mosasaurus. Sleek as a bullet and seemingly as fast, the Mosasaurus will have the potential to reach speeds of up to 24 knots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devil</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/devil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/devil/</guid>
      <description>Devil is designed to be a fun tech gadget by employing microphone and speaker function. With the bluetooth connection with smart phone, people can hold it and enjoy singing Karaoke songs streaming online. Bring AGIO Plus Devil with you to enjoy Karaoke whenever, wherever you are. The additional features for example SOS alarm, cute style, safe material, light and handy design make AGIO Plus Devil also a fabulous gift for children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyper</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/hyper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/hyper/</guid>
      <description>Hyper, EXA2, is a air freshener, aimed to optimize the in-car air quality. With the auto-front mimic design, quick clip, patterned air-refreshing technologies, Hyper will integrate into auto interior easily and make the diving experience more cozy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Series</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/a-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/a-series/</guid>
      <description>A series is a air freshener product line, aimed to optimize the in-car air quality. With the simple metal finish, quick clip, patterned air-refreshing technologies, A series will integrate into auto interior easily and make the diving experience more cozy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>G Series</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/g-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/g-series/</guid>
      <description>G series is a gel air freshener product line, aimed to optimize the in-car air quality. Can be fitted into the drink holder or attached to the dashboard. With the patterned formula, G series&amp;rsquo;s refershing gel won&amp;rsquo;t melt or spell over under any extreme climate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/ice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/ice/</guid>
      <description>Spring, the cation disinfection liquid atomizer, is aimed to clean up the in-door air rapidly within a simple touch. The transparent crystal appearance make the operation proccess visible not only for the functoinal benefit but provide an amusing atmosphere when lighting up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fort</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/fort/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/fort/</guid>
      <description>What if your dashcam didn&amp;rsquo;t just record your track, but actually connect to your smartphone to sync the data and charge it at the same time? What if it learned your driving habits, helped set alarm, then reminded you with smart, real-time actionable intelligence? Fort is a break new dashcam concept, equipped with Qi wireless charging standard and latest ADAS technology, make your driving experience more smoothly and brilliant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blueprint</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/blueprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/blueprint/</guid>
      <description>Blueprint Bag changes the concept we cast on this kind of items in the past&amp;ndash; occupy lots of space and only single function, combined with space you can take in professional designer&amp;rsquo;s stationeries and basic commodities, we design a new type of bag to meet specific roles in specific situations. This comprehensively designed bag allows to putting in artworks, blueprints, posters, used while commuting, working situations; also very suitable for outdoor recreation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thunder</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/thunder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/thunder/</guid>
      <description>Thunder is a dustproof, waterproof (IP68), plunge ready action cam. Designed to provide fearless drop, shock and impact protection that exceeds military standards. Most of all, you can record anywhere life takes you and not have to worry about whether your camera will survive your next epic adventure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blackwidow</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/blackwidow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 22:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/blackwidow/</guid>
      <description>Blackwidow is a dashcam designed to enhance the lifestyle of driving. The dashcam connects to user&amp;rsquo;s phone to preview and store the footage through Wifi. Integrated with intelligent functions such as FCWS, LDWS, ADAS, and rear lens, Blackwidow becomes Exspider&amp;rsquo;s 2017 flagship product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/chameleon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 22:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/chameleon/</guid>
      <description>Chameleon is the first FullHD 2&amp;rdquo; dashcam designed for Exspider brand. The camera-level components and changable colorful front cover make dashcam not only a reliable product but a delicate product which can meet consumer&amp;rsquo;s favor easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyclops</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/cyclops/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 22:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/cyclops/</guid>
      <description>Cyclops is the smallest FullHD Wi-Fi dashcam in the world (L52mm x W49mm x H39mm). Equipped with ADAS function, Cyclops not only inherits the sport car feature line but provides a fabulous use experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>F1</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/f1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 22:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/f1/</guid>
      <description>F1 is the FullHD 2.4&amp;rdquo; dashcam provided with built-in GPS module. It mimics the sport car&amp;rsquo;s feature line, shape and speed of processing data as well. The well design cooling structure also make CR2000 a big impact to market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reaper</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/reaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 22:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/reaper/</guid>
      <description>Whether screwing nails, cutting lines or simply opening a bottle, the Reaper multi-funtion gear can do it all! Thanks to the ring, it can be attached anywhere and is always there when you need it. A great gift and a handy helping hand for excursions, travel and small repairs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robocop</title>
      <link>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/robocop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 22:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chienwei0319.github.io/portfolio/robocop/</guid>
      <description>Robocop is a 5&amp;rdquo; FullHD dashcam merging the rear view mirror with camera function. With the Android os system, police radar detector, GPS module included, Robocop become a mighty full function tech gear. Furthermore, there are two types of design, one designed to replace your current rear view mirror; the other designed to attach by rubber band, which is more convenient to assemble.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>